

hr@jiholee.me https://jiholee.me Austin, TX, 78729 (737) 326-8040



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jiho-lee-dev

SUMMARY

Authorized to work in the United States for any employer: GC (Green Card)

20+ years of Full-stack developer and former designer; experience designing and developing front and back-end small and large projects. In a rapidly developing modern IT environment, always keep trying to learn and understand the flow of new technology. Regardless of platform, able to quickly hands-on and apply a variety of languages, libraries, and frameworks.

EXPERIENCE

Mar 2020 - Oct 2022 • Senior Software Engineer Project Lead

Natureware, Inc. Cypress California, US

Lead our team on its journey to create innovative e-commerce management products for our customers. Improved DevOps cycles to handle efficient and automated repetitive tasks to reduce unnecessarily wasted resources, saving manpower, time, and cost. Create next-generation e-commerce PWA products, customers, supply chain, inventory, product items, orders, shipment, accounts, API Gateway, and desktop app.

Jan 2019 - Mar 2020 • Senior Full Stack Developer

GIT Hyundai KIA Motor Group Irvine California, US

Vehicle diagnostic solution. DevOps inspection management system integrates Web, Mobile, Desktop App, API WebService, SOAP, XML, JSON, on .NET framework.

Nov 2010 - Dec 2018 • Senior Full Stack Web Developer

Lafestar, Inc. Los Angeles California, US

B2B e-commerce marketplace with WooCommerce CMS WordPress, Magento, Shopify on AWS; others with LEMP, PHP, jQuery, ASP.NET MVC, .NET Core

Nov 2008 - Sep 2010 • Senior Web Developer

Wewelcom corp. Anyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea e-commerce solution classic ASP, C#.NET MSSQL, RESTful API, SOAP, XML

Aug 2005 - Nov 2008 • Web Developer

SEJONG Telecom (FMR. Onse Telecom) Seongnam, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea GIS Web Map Roadmate, Navigation Software, Traffic Road data MRO. IIS, JSP, ASP, MSSQL, Oracle, COM+ Sockets, MFC, C#.NET, Window WebForm, Ajax Mar 2004 - Aug 2005 • Assistant Engineer

Onse Telecom Seongnam, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea GIS SI business, Signal simulator, UI Design, PDA app, Window Mobile 2003

Jan 2002 - Mar 2004 • Designer & Developer

Seil I&C Gwanak-gu, Seoul, South Korea

Designed and Developed branding franchise websites web application on LAMP

TECHNIQUES

Front-end

HTML5, CSS3, SaaS, Less, JSS Bootstrap, Material UI, JavaScript, no-jQuery, ES6+, TypeScript SPA: Angular, React, Vue, Svelte, Remix, NextJS, Vite, Bun, PWA

Back-end

PHP, JSP, ASP, C#.NET, Java, Python, Ruby, GoLang, Node.js Web: IIS, Apache, Tomcat, Nginx Framework: CI, Laravel, Django, Flask, Rails, Spring Boot, NestJS DB: MSSQL, MySQL, MariaDB, Postgres, Redis, ElasticSerch NoSQL: MongoDB, CosmosDB API: RESTful API, XML, JSON, GraphQL, Prisma, RealM, Hasura

DevOps

Cloud: AWS, Azure, GCP, Heroku CI/CD: GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket Netlify, Jenkins, Travis, CircleCl Env: VM, Docker, Kubernetes

CMS

WordPress, WooCommerce, Magento, Shopify, GatsbyJS

Etcetera

Cross Hybrid: Ionic, React Native, Flutter, ElectronJS, Tauri, AMQP Automation: Pandas, Puppeteer ML: Tensorflow, Keras, OpenCV GTD, SDLC Agile Scrum Sprint Figma, Jira, ClickUp, Notion

see more > https://jiholee.me

EDUCATION

Mar 2015 - Sep 2018

Pacific States University

Los Angeles California, US

Bachelor of Science, Computer Information Systems

Jan 2011 - Mar 2015

Santa Monica College

Santa Monica California, US

Associate of Science, Computer Programming